dazzleyellowpages.com 2009-06-19

# DazzleYellowPages.com - Privacy Policy

| 

|     
---  
**Privacy Policy of DazzleYellowPages.com**  

Dazzle Yellow Pages respects your right to privacy. **This privacy policy applies only to the privacy of users of the dazzleyellowpages.com.comweb site. It does not apply to the offline activities of Shyam InfoNet. or any of its affiliates.** **Privacy Policy Effective Date / Updates**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 13, 2006. Our business changes constantly. This Privacy Policy will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of material changes to our Privacy Policy, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our web site frequently to see recent changes. Notice of any changes to this Privacy Policy shall be given by posting the version of the Privacy Policy containing such changes on this web site. **What information does the Web site gather?**

When you visit this site you may provide information on two different levels about your visit: 

|  |  Anonymous statistics collected as you browse the site  
---|---  
|  Personal information you knowingly give us  
  
Please be assured that we do not collect personal information about you from the website unless you provide it to us. This means that you can visit our Web sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself (such as your e-mail address). 

As you browse the site, our web servers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Via web server logs, we monitor statistics such as:

|   How many people visit our site  
---|---  
|   Which pages people visit on our site  
|   From which domains our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, google.com, yahoo.com)  
|   Which browsers people use to visit our site  
  
None of this information is associated with you as an individual (see information about cookies below). We use these statistics to improve our Web site, to monitor its performance, and to make the Web site easier for you and other visitors to use. 

**What about pages that ask for personal information?**   
When visitors supply information about themselves for a specific purpose, we use the information for that purpose (such as to provide the service or information the visitor has requested). For example, you may be asked to give us individual information to purchase a product or service, receive information, manage online account registration, or apply for a job. The information may range from your zip code, to your phone number, account number, a credit card number, age, gender, mother's maiden name, social security number, e-mail address, organization URL, resume, or mailing address.

When visitors use our Web site to order services, we may use this personally identifiable information as we would use the same information obtained in a traditional non-electronic manner. For example, to publish your name, address, and phone number in our directories (unless you have requested a non-published number), or to evaluate your service needs and contact you regarding additional services you may find useful. If you do not want us to contact you, you can remove your name from our telephone or mail solicitation lists by clicking on [Contact Us](http://www.dazzleyellowpages.com/Contact/). Please note that this removes your name from dazzleyellowpages.com, however, to be removed from other websites in the Shyam InfoNet family of companies, contact them directly.

Dazzle Yellow Pages does not knowingly collect information from children through this web site. This web site, and any web site to which users may link from this web site, may contain content provided by advertisers or other third parties that may not be suitable for children. Dazzle Yellow Pages asks parents or legal guardians to assist Dazzle Yellow Pages by supervising the activities of children at this web site. 

**What happens to information when I fill out registration forms?**   
The registration forms request accurate contact information (like name and e-mail address) and preferences that help us better serve you. Your name and e-mail address are used to send you information about our company, product updates, special offers, and newsletters. You may change your email, user ID or password online; or you can choose to remove your name from our user list by going to Contact Us and emailing us a request to remove your name. 

To improve the services we can offer you, we may decide to expand the site's capabilities for obtaining information about users in the future. We will update this privacy statement as policies change to ensure that you are aware of developments in this area. 

**Do you sell or give my information to companies outside of the "Dazzle Yellow Pages Family?"**   
We do not sell or disclose personally identifiable information obtained online about our visitors, to anyone outside of the "Dazzle Yellow Pages Family" unless you specifically authorize it, to complete a transaction that you initiated, it is required by law, or disclosure is necessary to protect the safety of customers, employees or property. If you provide personally identifiable information to us in the context of an event Dazzle Yellow Pages sponsors with another company, such as a contest, or if you register on a co-sponsored site or feature, you may also be providing the personally identifiable information to the co-sponsor. This will be made clear to you before you submit the information and you can decide whether or not to participate. 

Dazzle Yellow Pages may share non-personally identifiable information with non-"Dazzle Yellow Pages Family" companies in order to assess the results of a promotion, event or third party relationship, to provide information to current or prospective customers, to complete a search or to otherwise enhance your online experience. For example, we may provide statistical information that is not identified with you: 

|  |  The number of people who visit the website, which pages were visited and for how long, the referral URL, the user's IP address, and the User Agent.  
---|---|---  
|   |  When we host co-branded versions of the dazzleyellowpages.com site (or portions of the dazzleyellowpages.com site). Our co-branded sites may also contain clear GIFs (electronic images that allow this site to collect anonymous information about your visit to the site).  
|   |  Non-personally identifiable information may also be disclosed to non-Dazzle Yellow Pages-Family companies if it is required by law, or disclosure is necessary to protect the safety of customers, employees or property.  
  
**This does not contain any information that would personally identify you.** In addition, Dazzle Yellow Pages may support features and content that appear on other companies' web sites that you may visit. These companies may collect information about you, but Dazzle Yellow Pages does not have control over the collection practices of these companies. If you are visiting a web site that indicates that it is "powered by dazzleyellowpages.com.com," you are advised to read the privacy policy of that web site for its policies regarding information collection and usage. 

**Does this site send e-mail to site visitors?**   
At times, online surveys are conducted in which you can choose to participate. In addition, we may use e-mail to communicate with our customers, to respond to visitors' e-mail, to confirm orders placed online, and to send information that a visitor has requested. Occasionally, we may use opt-in e-mail lists from third parties to promote our latest specials. If you receive an unwanted e-mail from us, you can click Contact Us and simply ask us to remove you from our list. 

**Do you accommodate links to other sites?**   
This website contains links to other web sites. These other web sites may, among other things, allow you to bid on and/or purchase products that you initially viewed on this web site. These other web sites may (or may not) be co-branded with Dazzle Yellow Pages or dazzleyellowpages.com.com branding. **You can tell if you have linked from one web site to another web site by looking at the URL in the browser window. If the second level domain of the URL for the page containing the link is different than the second level domain of the URL for the page to which you have linked, you have linked to a different web site. For example, if you link from a page located at the URL _www.thirdleveldomain.dazzleyellowpages.com.com_ to a page located at the URL _www.dazzleyellowpages.com.secondleveldomain.com_ , you have linked to another site. Please note that any of Dazzle Yellow Pages's trademarks or service marks (e.g., dazzleyellowpages.com) may be included in the URL of a co-branded or private label web site that is owned and operated by a third party, in a location other than that occupied by the second level domain (e.g., as the third level domain).**   The companies that own or operate these web sites may track and/or collect information about you, but Dazzle Yellow Pages does not have control over the privacy practices (including, without limitation, those relating to tracking user activity, collection of user data, use of user data, and security) of these companies (although, when a user activates a link from this web site one of these other web sites, Dazzle Yellow Pages may pass the user's referral URL and IP address to the server hosting such other site). We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices (including, without limitation, those related to tracking, collection, use and security) employed by (or in connection with) other sites, and we are not responsible for the content on, or operation of, other sites (including, without limitation, any transactions conducted through such other sites). We are committed to safeguarding customer privacy on our website. **If you are visiting a web site via a link on this web site, you are advised to read the privacy policy of that other web site for its policies regarding information tracking, collection, usage and security.**

**What is Dazzle Yellow Pages's position regarding online advertising and third party ad servers?**  
Dazzle Yellow Pages accepts advertisements from third parties that serve advertising into the dazzleyellowpages.com sites. Dazzle Yellow Pages may use "clear gifs" provided by such third parties in the pages containing the ad(s) that Dazzle Yellow Pages sends to your browser. These "clear gifs" provide usage pattern information about the ads to third parties. The data does not contain personally identifiable information. 

As part of the online advertising process, we may use information supplied from third party ad serving companies as well as other third party companies in several ways such as to:

|  |  gain a better understanding of the type of individuals viewing or visiting different web sites  
---|---|---  
|   |  evaluate and prioritize site selection when developing online media plan  
|   |  geographically target advertising  
|   |  deliver product and pricing advertising/information applicable to the customers' state  
|   |  gauge the effectiveness of our online advertising  
  
**  
Non Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically**   
A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique User ID for our Web site. Cookies help us to identify returning visitor's to our websites, which allows us to give you a more personalized, useful experience on our website. 

Cookies help Dazzle Yellow Pages to enhance the user's online experience and are used to: 

|  |  deliver the appropriate geographic message  
---|---|---  
|   |  manage frequency of ad exposure; avoid over delivery of the same message  
|   |  tailor an advertisement to better match your interests and preferences  
|   |  ensure that you see the correct products and pricing applicable to the state in which you live  
|   |  understand advertising effectiveness  
  
However, customers are free to delete website cookies. Most internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. To disable cookies, see "Setting Cookie Preferences" at the end of this policy. 

However, you need to understand that some websites/ad serving companies have the ability to reestablish your history even after cookie deletion, if you reenter the same site on another occasion, or some other site tracked by the ad serving company/network, and specifically provide personal data. 

Deletion of cookies alone does not prevent ad serving companies from reestablishing history on a visitor. The visitor must either continue to decline cookies each time it reenters the site to keep the tracking severed, if desired, or opt-out. When you opt-out, your unique user ID cookie is erased and you are reassigned an anonymous, non-id cookie. This new cookie tells websites that you have opted out and they will then know not to attempt to assign other cookies to you in the future. Opt-out cookies do not contain a unique user ID number therefore websites are not able to identify your computer uniquely. 

Customers who choose to continually delete cookies and not opt out can have their browser advise them each time a web site attempts to send a cookie to your system. At that time, you can choose to either Accept or Cancel a cookie. 

Customers who choose to "opt out" after deleting cookies will receive an anonymous/non personally identifiable cookie.

**Does Dazzle Yellow Pages use the information provided online to profile its customers?**   
The combination of offline and online information provided by the customer has the ability to enhance the customer experience, and make the consumer's interaction with Dazzle Yellow Pages more meaningful and relevant. Dazzle Yellow Pages requires notification of any consumer profiling or purchasing behavior being captured by Dazzle Yellow Pages online and combined with offline information be clearly stated to the consumer at the time of online data collection. The consumer will have the ability to choose not to have that information aggregated and be part of subsequent marketing campaigns by so indicating at the point of the application, or by choosing to Opt-Out of future marketing campaigns from Dazzle Yellow Pages by clicking on [Contact Us](http://www.dazzleyellowpages.com/Contact/). 

**Please note:**   
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served relating to our web site. 

**How do I know I am on a secured site?**   
Every secure page on this web site has been secured with a digital certificate. You know you are on a secure page of this web site when you see a lock in the status bar at the bottom of your browser. In Internet Explorer, you can view your status bar by clicking on View, Status Bar. When you see the lock, double click it and a popup window opens and displays who issued the digital certificate securing that page and the dates it is valid. 

**How does Dazzle Yellow Pages prevent unauthorized access to my account information?**   
Your password is set at a minimum of six characters, which provides added protection for your personal information. On secured pages, this site uses SSL encryption up to 128-bits. 

**What security measures are in place to restrict access to personal data?**   
There are a variety of security measures in place that limits internal access to data stored by the Dazzle Yellow Pages site. Access is restricted to authorized personnel only and requires an employee to have a secure ID and password to access the information. In addition, logs are reviewed regularly to spot any inconsistencies. The site is continually updated with the latest known security patches that are periodically published by the system vendor. Any information that you give is password protected. For your protection, the system automatically locks out a user after 3 incorrect tries and after 20 minutes of idle time per secure session. If you forget your password, you will be prompted to supply your customer ID number and your password will be e-mailed to you. 

**What information is stored by the site or in cookies?**   
Registration information, bill and online shopping, data and contact e-mail addresses are stored in Dazzle Yellow Pages databases which are physically secure environments that are not accessible via the Internet. This information is only available to you through the use of a secure ID and password, and the information is transferred from our databases for your viewing. 

A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique User ID for our web site. Cookies help us to identify returning visitor's to our web sites, which allow us to give you a more personalized, useful experience on our web site. We use cookies for purposes such as delivering web content specific to your interests, and to keep track of your order as you order services. A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you do not want us to establish and maintain a unique Dazzle Yellow Pages.com User ID. Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions on this web site, such as My Directory. To disable cookies, see next section. 

**Here is How to Set Your Cookie Preferences:**

|  |  Netscape Navigator 3.x: In the Options menu, select Network Preferences. In Network Preferences, click on the Protocols tab and there you may choose to be warned before accepting cookies.  
---|---|---  
|   |  Netscape Navigator 4.x: In the Edit menu, select Preferences. In the Preferences dialog box, in the left hand side menu, click on 'Advanced' and 4 options concerning cookies appear on the lower right. Choose Help for further details. You can find more information about cookies and Netscape on the Netscape web site.  
|   |  Microsoft Internet Explorer 3.x: In the view menu, select Options. Click on Advanced tab. You may choose to be warned before accepting cookies.  
|   |  Microsoft Internet Explorer 4.x: In the view menu, select Options. Click on Advanced tab and scroll down to a yellow triangle icon with an exclamation labeled "Cookies" where you have 3 options.  
|   |  Other Browsers: Contact the manufacturer of the browser for information.  

|  Fill in almost any combination of fields:  
---  
Keyword:  
Business Name:  
Street:  
Location  (City, State, Country)  
Phone  
Dazzle Just this category   
Show  matches per page
